<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CountryProject</string>
    <string name="Bangladesh_text">

        The riverine country of Bangladesh (“Land of the Bengals”) is one of the most densely populated countries in the world, and its people are predominantly Muslim.\n
        As the eastern portion of the historical region of Bengal, the area once formed, along with what is now the Indian state of West Bengal, the province of Bengal in British India.\n
        With the partition of India in 1947, it became the Pakistani province of East Bengal (later renamed East Pakistan), one of five provinces of Pakistan, separated from the other four by 1,100 miles (1,800 km) of Indian territory.\n
        In 1971 it became the independent country of Bangladesh, with its capital at Dhaka.

        \n\n\n\n\n

        The riverine country of Bangladesh (“Land of the Bengals”) is one of the most densely populated countries in the world, and its people are predominantly Muslim.\n
        As the eastern portion of the historical region of Bengal, the area once formed, along with what is now the Indian state of West Bengal, the province of Bengal in British India.\n
        With the partition of India in 1947, it became the Pakistani province of East Bengal (later renamed East Pakistan), one of five provinces of Pakistan, separated from the other four by 1,100 miles (1,800 km) of Indian territory.\n
        In 1971 it became the independent country of Bangladesh, with its capital at Dhaka.




    </string>
    <string name="India_text">

        India, country that occupies the greater part of South Asia.\n
        Its capital is New Delhi, built in the 20th century just south of the historic hub of Old Delhi to serve as India’s administrative centre.\n
        Its government is a constitutional republic that represents a highly diverse population consisting of thousands of ethnic groups and likely hundreds of languages.\n
        With roughly one-sixth of the world’s total population, India is the second most populous country, after China.

        \n\n\n\n\n

        India, country that occupies the greater part of South Asia.\n
        Its capital is New Delhi, built in the 20th century just south of the historic hub of Old Delhi to serve as India’s administrative centre.\n
        Its government is a constitutional republic that represents a highly diverse population consisting of thousands of ethnic groups and likely hundreds of languages.\n
        With roughly one-sixth of the world’s total population, India is the second most populous country, after China.



    </string>
    <string name="Pakistan_text">

        Pakistan, populous multiethnic country of South Asia.\n
        Having a predominately Indo-Iranian speaking population, Pakistan has historically and culturally been associated with its neighbours Iran, Afghanistan, and India.\n
        Since Pakistan and India achieved independence in 1947, Pakistan has been distinguished from its larger southeastern neighbour by its overwhelmingly Muslim population (as opposed to the predominance of Hindus in India).\n
        Pakistan has struggled throughout its existence to attain political stability and sustained social development.\n
        Its capital is Islamabad, in the foothills of the Himalayas in the northern part of the country, and its largest city is Karachi, in the south on the coast of the Arabian Sea.

        \n\n\n\n\n

        Pakistan, populous multiethnic country of South Asia.\n
        Having a predominately Indo-Iranian speaking population, Pakistan has historically and culturally been associated with its neighbours Iran, Afghanistan, and India.\n
        Since Pakistan and India achieved independence in 1947, Pakistan has been distinguished from its larger southeastern neighbour by its overwhelmingly Muslim population (as opposed to the predominance of Hindus in India).\n
        Pakistan has struggled throughout its existence to attain political stability and sustained social development.\n
        Its capital is Islamabad, in the foothills of the Himalayas in the northern part of the country, and its largest city is Karachi, in the south on the coast of the Arabian Sea.


    </string>
</resources>